

SHAH

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Graphic Design

Motion Graphic

Web Design

2D Animation

About me:

Experienced graphic designer with 11 years in the industry. Keenly interested in front-end development and UI design. Known for a strong work ethic, passion for learning, and a drive for excellence in competitive environments.

Name Muhammad Shahril Fadzlyn

Bin Baharin

Language Malay • Native

English • Basic

CONTACT

Mobile 016 - 9191 002

E-mail shahrilfadzlyn@gmail.com

Website shahrilfadzlyn.github.io/portfolio

Address 11, Jalan Wangsa 1/3,

Taman Wangsa Permai, 52200, Kuala Lumpur

REFERENCE

Name Mr. S S Loong

Position Manager of Prepress Dept.

Mobile 017 - 692 1538

Address UPA PRESS SDN. BHD.

Lot 8228, Batu 6½, Jalan Kuchai Lama 58200 Kuala Lumpur.



WORK EXPERIENCE

2017 - Present UPA Press Sdn. Bhd.

Graphic Designer (Freelance)

Locum Net Asia Sdn. Bhd **Graphic Designer** (Freelance)

Jawi Streetwear

Graphic Designer (Self-employed)

2017 - 2018 SF Motion Studio

2D Animator (Self-employed)

2014 - 2017 UPA Press Sdn. Bhd.

Graphic Designer (Permanent)

2013 - 2014 iProduksi

2D Animator (Freelance)

FNF Printing

Graphic Designer (Self-employed)

Vermilion Concept

Wedding Photographer (Self-employed)

2011 DotPerInchStudio

Graphic Designer (Internship)



EDUCATION

2011 - 2013 Ba (hons) Media Practice with Animation

Second Class Honours (Upper Division)

University of the West of England, United Kingdom

2008 - 2011 Diploma in Digital Media Design

CGPA 3.67

Kolej Kemahiran Tinggi MARA Rembau

2006 - 2007 **SPM; 1A, 3B, 2C, 2D, 1E** SMK Sri Tasik, Kuala Lumpur



ACHIEVEMENT

2015 Best Performance Award

UPA Press Sdn Bhd.

2014 Best Performance Award

UPA Press Sdn Bhd.

2010 **1st Place winner**, Graphic Design Technology,

Malaysia Skills Competition, 19th

Best Artwork Award, Digital Media, 5th Semester

Kolej Kemahiran Tinggi MARA Rembau

All Rounder Best Artwork Award

Kolej Kemahiran Tinggi MARA Rembau

Note; Nemanilan Tinggi Fizak



TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Suite

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Flash/Animate, After Effects, Premiere & Audition

Microsoft Office Suite Word, Excel & Powerpoint Coding

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Other Software/App

Figma, VSCode, Canva, Capcut,

ChatGPT 4



MUHAMMAD SHAHRIL FADZLYN BIN BAHARIN

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer

UPA Press Sdn. Bhd. 2017 - Present (*Freelance*) 2014 - 2017 (*Permanent*)

- Responsible for designing table calendars and diaries for both domestic and international clients.
- Reviewing and correcting the format, color, and layout of artwork received from customers before printing.
- Maintaining consistent communication with customers until the artwork is finalized.
- Operating laser cutting and prepress printing machines to provide color proofs and mock-up samples for customers.
- Collaborated closely with the sales team, supervisors, and production manager on every project.
- Actively participated in the Research & Development team for our new products.
- Responsible for photographing our latest product lines.
- Shared knowledge and mentored junior graphic designers.
- · Actively contributed to our website development.

Graphic Designer (Freelance)

Locum Net Asia Sdn. Bhd. | 2021 - Present

- Responsible:
 - > Create corporate identity.
 - > Involved in creating UI and UX for our app.
 - > Create a video advertisement to showcase our app.
 - > Create marketing material.

Graphic Designer (Self-employed)

Jawi Streetwear | 2021 - 2022

- Responsible:
 - > Create brand identity.
 - > Conduct product research & development.
 - Dealing with supplier.
 - > Create social media & website.
 - > Create content & marketing material.
 - > Capturing images of products.
 - > Entertain prospects and customers.

2D Animator (Self-employed) SF Motion Studio | 2017 - 2018

- Create 2D animation content on Facebook & Youtube.
- Provides 2D animation & graphic design service for international customer on Fiverr, a global online marketplace.

2D Animator (Freelance)

iProduksi | 2013 - 2014

- Responsible to develop concept art & producing 2 - 3 minutes of an animated music video for a campaign on TV3.
- Responsible to develop concept art & producing an animated pilot episode for our cartoon series.

Wedding photographer (Self-employed)

Vermilion Concept | 2013 - 2014

• Responsible to take pictures for a wedding ceremony.

Graphic Designer (Self-employed)

FNF Printing | 2013 - 2014

- · Responsible:
 - > Create corporate identity.
 - Create designs for bunting, banner, business card, T-shirt & logo our customer.